got over Dokdo 18 so before we start I
just wanted to give you an update
no talk manage new homes Casa is my casa
fine we got my gloves over - oh no my
store he's been taking instability
Potamus bring him up in the air about it
he feels and surrani who's been taking
care of and feels on this where I knew
and check it out I didn't do much time
but yeah that's what should play in the
DC jail better infection could infect
acerra me everything is fine no burst of
bad stuff so her - or rest assure that I
felt strongly yeah but she better show a
crashing moment a bullet center quake my
man it's not just a youngster it's very
much a purgatory said the prana standard
catharsis for me they had the most
suitable I didn't you complain Manoj
stolen especially of a child of a child
but what would be the antidote for us
it's the template that we do not then
that's it it's almost imagine five
minute meditation on so it's rustic its
mill Jewish stance about Geshe Michaels
this Terry
way of bringing these these beautiful
teachings into the world
don't cognition Michael but researchers
academic session its CEO Cheney
apprenticeship Amir even us touch those
on the your the NAM deep understanding a
single book herbs in Romania
American a pedometer but yeah but darker
at Oreo announced our name is Eliot Ness
Culkin much said the boy he and I think
in a few minutes and just read they were
stationed abroad para Mina's
bus lady miss person just just stops the
shows about this eh don't love us leach
Nadal stole money to desert and the my
and rejoice in that when yet just
someone to chariot Kotori JC was that
seprieono that there was a little bit
more of a distance of time from here
it was amazing to discover the brain so
much that was but that'll continue for
and give yes could coming out procedures
you but don't don't gather this gift
we're learning stone my chili deep the
universal principles that's the motion
its it go boy cured army she hates it
but we can see our lives improving in
murder movies me so I was raised in uh
Schmidt I wish him good
it's interpreter I see Morris area your
prices he mostly Hiroshi a seminar so
let's take the way the first thing is
coming out stellar my gift
Kotori much me that's our practice
stronger powerful gift - but that'll
commercial practical
so we're at the final SEO class it's
called correct view
quickly read through ya boisterous notes
get taken and gives you a really spoke
on all the points already love me
emphasize them for issues class but I
jump she doesn't have any of the points
that this cover ready to provide a
bishop there's questions since there was
leftover sale okay it's so in the
process of produces genius to talk about
nineveh's Dania mark mark mark did it he
just had to do this we done good
business daily
was it the see things I mean actually
the principal is to see that these are
coming from you it's a really good CV
should good police positive us how does
it machine so unfair no chest me things
are all kosher nation as we understand
this item is two realities we really
expressing this realities in the same
space right Wayne the sounds are well
when we leave a register when you teach
it is it - it's a lab is good for year
the puppy comes into the room that what
is it yes welcome
and if any say madam star is right nice
and rough or is it which kinetic
Roshan's usually people get both are
right to our famous what should share
dad misses and the chew toys really a
beautiful metaphor but yet caucus in the
heroin these two men a man coexisted a
delicious words mister sit down what
about other rooms that thank you
you know we know these rooms exist trust
the description I'm stood through Kimura
people coming to Utica Varela I went to
the forum realm like it yeah incredible
yeah there's a show of stead of quite a
while my boy this is ninety bollocks
video but unless you have a better
perception of the is nettle it has
to be taken what Ithaca visa yes okay we
believe that the Scriptures are
seriously it's just towards but nobody
even the state of Nirvana
- is staying in Univ honest even the
state of Nirvana any of you who could be
under boys violets book with me - she
creates him the whole room and
I searched a niche the perceptual really
but with Attila sufficient already
unless it's not what's somewhere else
and I think you're sure they're damaged
this person is master stop babies of
adage that the maximum I suggest I do is
to besiege us and so these two truths we
have there you know are we in a sense
stuck in the conventional truth or what
we labeled the other day as deceptive
truth is the basis to experience of
lightness very much you know you have
you have intellectual perception but it
was pets in the whole point of what
we're teaching about emptiness that's
here at the toilet bunions and any of
the schools just get those seeds to
dismiss him in that reminding us I mean
that's a - this is totally not doing
this it's totally mere press was it
Esmond young and when we study emptiness
that message and it was nice sister so
this case esteemeth one thing gives you
Michael remember osha question question
what's on your mind means it bastard a
monolith I wrote my show my search I'm
already of those seeds prevents I just
threw a sim man this shade less actual
yes going to the lower row must have
been yep up by Stephanie she attained a
rebirthing
NEPA - that's an issue Sarah and that's
a remarkable gift it but she's not sure
about that hands in our heads around
yes I'm gonna stay syllabi Milne and
understand these ultimate two realities
ultimate and conventional or deceptive
reality instantly absolutely am i
jealous to anybody and that about the
flesh himself dying him is more but that
of a question to Atlanta then yes the
magellan but that you know that we're on
the right track we're not letting up
it's here and that's where the
laboratory of life kicks in and we begin
the practice in the thoracic Aziz Nesin
are so mission I it's normal
Davonte traffic juice y-drop kami and
what they constipation as a Boromir all
the above we have to remember this shows
that ups the mind am maybe three to five
thousand times a day Olivia special on
your mother but they're less distressed
reasonability right I guess that's more
Srivastava it's so much to say sometimes
we have to do this like you know there's
no but you know it's it's just like
going to the Hilton gym right I think
good what the way I lives in your mind
is okay i restrain myself I won't let
that emotion overcharge yeah think about
that measure essentially
always does that I am certainly zero
mess with it see what seems to be best
that I am ception this silly monster
flatness very much we are depriving the
moms it came home prism a samosas the
last visit registered I knew position if
we could really yes Lima live at the
station land but yet we will talk about
yoga very much fantasy Slovak Sammy near
Toronto beside each tablet directors
sounds in the visit Istanbul which
nobody you asked me about today miss but
I see that with a piece of wood now then
we've have some really foundational
launchpad to go into our world every day
if the ganas whitaker brothers could be
the best mr. Amash offensive Mirta
kyochon shortcut you gotta I gotta see
baby see a mining fields of a given day
you know I got I became a news junkie
recently yeah
a style of razor but that key my
Saturday no mrs. Jenner like when I'm
not listening to any given day in the
White House no killing but novice tip
rod I'm bailing don't like I need to
hear this is to me is no specialist
oppress what it made a time I I mean I I
do I realize that I kept in my own store
at the first it's pure almost gossip
right it is displaying show the actual
essence to the Cheney identify I've
messed that that was going on inside our
country mr. so punish the police wasn't
you don't necessarily it was me unless I
know that there is a phase change my
surfaced yeah dude I see bear - yeah
hydras national assembly's waves
agenda sound daily across the sanctions
regime very dramatic and very rama
shockingly if the shiny kira show and
you want safe excitatory
so Buster there's like I have certain
drive it's a yeah you know maybe my test
today will be when I'm starting
what and the lady good thing could she
if they're sure what I do teaching on
emptiness from say see that's my
struggles I'm like yeah that over bitty
better note set them is how many I could
I could I support that shorter the
fixing of an election in 2016 is minutes
at oppressed a decisive understand like
if she was teaching us by night so
that's what she asked in German go to my
yard waste them but Abajo Vidya try some
video to get a free car wash you know it
doesn't is a graph Kia or revisit or
that the Monica studio a transient as
mr. DiPalma smashing this one this
specimen of a stimulus event made a
person this process on the human
presence stop evil production team
organism estimates of my true identity
Diamond Mountain is kind of beautiful
hey damnit mom tell you the rescue
master yeah Internet the ones that the
horse don't ask you something that is
you know the the seduction is there to
go online and what that's not relevant
to what your retreat is all over I'm
cautious serve as a team and that
facilitate so much other nights it yes
the Magellan time I can assume intimate
when you know when you see the direct
perception of it when he stepped in
assume one message may not everything
you've done up to the point of seeing
emptiness has contributed to a soldier
stove instead adored or mentor
especially unfortunately Thomas the poet
was
see the much cannibalizing concern that
I want to say exactly shame it does say
yeah just same as it does secondary of
these are so at my guys from welcome in
the constant compliment videos posted on
the free movies it's very honest and we
don't see that we may feature my return
doing the work we're not family prestige
elementary body for the turbulent honing
book and how many hours I do with
meditation
uh yeah moreover Sydney needs but yeah
that's it but I also miss it's a
skullcap prosocial Rockefeller or
experiencing I don't I'm personally
saying this we're not experiencing
radical change in our practice to like
the medial and some of practicum a nice
put fatigue is not required it's they
all growing restive I am a professional
karma so described a sociable istra
having a trial yet the table structures
near the Prophet Elisha maestra Roger
gas which is a monstrous beast
approaches the shore upon story the
Karma no word stroke or she wastrels was
it something that I thank you it just
they're too much though values Natasha
technical tour of any of our privacy
policy in chess mr. oceanbring's if
that's a five days just Rocco and I see
be quite incredible visually buddy
biblically in the soy of ice-blue kajita
petrissage she has come in OTC me now
every sauce the linen staying on the
other at the blog addressed by evil
devices that emotion she said a little
bit that's a relief that's if
were similar to was Bob and the harsh
focus not be acceptable small if I don't
study that or even made of stabilizers
that I should I
beside it is the baddest come up with
money devoted service I did this way the
start of drogas provides a Russian CSS
total univariate every class they may
not able to represent not a much the
epitome of expression that are most
particularly now when you - period say
was that the Athenians yes appropriate
server that is this the first of us
beautifully kinda hours ever don't
waiting at the stubble store that the
story that is just so unbelievably thank
you very yeah can I have another eight
hours next week three ethnic is Remus
that Dustin omits is bound the
practically theater with Sebastian face
above three clubs yeah that's a close so
it shows us a rough word before it was
Ian's word doc which is really robotics
yeah busted opacity may not become aware
again I would open yeah good yeah and
it's just a reality check for the truck
covers yet successively wanting to have
the direct reception oh no less than one
hour day yes I mean II had no chance of
Jane imagistic talk about no-brainer
Maxis me not tortimer Beauchamp I see I
practice that at the process to
Elizabeth ledge notice a same then
territory Buddhists in the bottom stock
perishable reverse three years in
answering service Masjid machine is
there already ATP revolt album not Delta
to chassis Liberty
yeah I think if teach other show you all
know Yoga is the perfect complement yo
guy that that way you know it's a
complement question is it that says
hotel systems like tai chi or Sheikh
Omar al Qaeda where you're really moving
Chi the your give him big it's about the
energy prana he uses for mirror its
effect on Coachella yet oh but she's
such a student laminated syllabus to
boost Rahul so divisive topic later time
so at the one into the end is one of
them Davos dollars the devil latest
movie post atoll in the bootcut eveson
name it happened it hours to be your
village but if you have the indirect
process
yes nervous history more experience a
building of the hires missile coordinate
I listed Pena - cool you disturb you
status that you don't wind up put an
opportune a lot of people are kind of
tuning into the six flavors of emptiness
in argument and evidence for the
sensitive of course of pasta think
beautiful at our change entry into the
street Hiroshi what man talk to purchase
transmitted the pasta talk Resnick's
calling your business into that
associated teaching it's a change
there's I think there's one main AC is
that masked I'm not practical happened
in 1998 innocent of California Tom will
is it online associates it was that
is a beautiful precise Shay I say
to rebrand us flavors in the midnight as
the school year but who service today
for six man doing one
never doing five move souvenir Magellan
my deal but I'm bad but I'm three in the
mapa stay on there to tell em as any
mine recently he swirls I'm sorry Ava's
Prieta loyal yeah when you mine yup or
statistic by Chivas Regal ultra and then
go on push if atoms atoms and knobs but
those we didn't miss attention go deeper
yes the flights at the post of Qaddafi
apostasy at the dancers margin:0 Jerry
Smith Acosta is chosen yet primero bleep
my you a mini our decisive as morning
the Tavor stubborn agenda at Miletus oh
man Minya in my human yes mate written
you know onions we she said yeah the end
we composited Dobson I detect it when
yeah Ragnar yet my path to get my guys I
get my exes Nonya where is Vijay yes
mafia my you are read at the dressage
image that's a new poster don't give
yourself a flea
yeah can take you to deeper but believer
at the dice tom was much less bicycle
option but Natasha snow concentrate so
what's the other side of the Tokaido
gastronomy antennas with that they the
flip side of the same coin
a chi of Dagestan yeah interdependence
or dependent origination service my
proscenium
we have to learn karma I'm losing our
budgets are cut in the realization of
karma it exerts a karma are also
equivalent I could have me the full ice
the full package
tell them or tell them to do but course
we can't use but Virginia direct
perception of emptiness
I says mania was so closer than it was
meeting later how many of you have not
heard the two husbands this is Vesna
social promotion I think we should still
do it I don't much to them there's no
sir it doesn't I still do it
yeah not yet not yet what's the chest
get ready in a minute but when I heard
it they have special at Singapore yes it
was just thing I don't want about the
crust engage me put it on it though it's
just put everything in perspective for
me a grownup respect even lemon young we
were also in a teaching in Beijing and
attention Beijing opera diet dambulla
and on the distance awesome today these
scholars from University of Beijing it
was just incredible why don't you add
was like this renowned scholar who had
written books you know like 28 books yes
said he he spoke for like an hour
on dal-su there's a chalice translate
instantly put us a bit of idea was just
like it was so abstract black man next
guess from microfinance and a steno talk
the two husbands because I was a mature
audience with 2800 people to teach
dependent origination mr. West mr. Choi
and I just remember the faces of these
to see a formalist of the Chilean sir
with a table splash yes sort of stuff
showing the audience and it was so
beautiful it was a moment
I think the audience kind of yeah the
most still lacks the authority that's
libelous it's just a bunch of the class
name on the door my sister
yes Porticus possible CAC transmitted
they did that saying what is go I don't
start this driving natural going yet it
was certainly unlike the Berlin
formation that the Boston Louisa and the
boy it's a list its lures nostalgia just
update in an origination
Dakshina Kannada literature at the Sun
that to me is Woodley manatees 150 200
times but you're the Spurs David Pakman
over us Abby's natural that is okay the
good news is yeah Hiroshi lewiston's
dong stuff says massive comelet's
officer kissed was mr. Ishihara shunova
staff doctor families lunar meet
watching her oh shoot but should ban
karo shoes to match the but these days
[Music]
passing a machine you visit that this
number was a mulatto boy Academy still
get the daughter I think you're in the
room I get a lot of comments in
biomechanics Kissimmee now this can a
happy news director both the visit
suppose just on the pyramid omniscient
mind even a very messy history tells us
that in the primer and if sick diameter
cars their custom I mean while they're
being
god I need says neither go out and
have fun and let's see who these in
Phoenix on Easter Sunday some kid is
crying because the Easter I said God in
chocolate wasn't your baby it's a
considered welcome the passbook a
terminal just have some chocolate in his
eyes oh my god you know there's so many
people having dinner alone so emissions
is justice about yet the perception give
me a chance of the body of the Buddha
that can emanate in any way an ice
planet terrible dr. Boustany Romania
Panetta who were three men's to you yet
privates you well some would sure for
more commercial ad hoc from the premiere
with ocean scene levator time at mount
he will have a winner cause vinco come
around you Kotori pleasure to graduate
me move Ashford or Mecca the other day
there was a beautiful rain at 4:00 a.m.
in the morning I thought it was gorgeous
though but coming up here the other day
non below those Irish names they come in
but yes Hiroshi is doctor put the
Mogadishu miss postman idiot they made
equanimity ravenous take are my goodness
could appear butum wasn't me it's a drag
a do that miss Vye my casual Chaitra
gazing across what people say interested
a little coverage to post a pizza yet
God my husband was so wise pasta Patil
yet posted as water for human
that is news took a community partner a
story yesterday on ballot evidence of
water stores nobody taught any Bimini a
lesbian yet document in a recent visit
dr. Okun no tourism agreement ons now
Estonia knows nobody does sure so it's
not like in pretty packages even if
SIGGRAPH hypocrisy' rose / - the topic
of common he pretty ugly mention please
avoided if the judge for that matter was
lenient the diversion yes they asked
that the Kodama stood in the key Horomia
it touches for Iran similar scribble
said she shared sermon with a vegetable
Rodriguez was maliciously versus Diana
so we said you know madam arranged oh I
didn't chess game including the
preliminaries still shy Portland of
Magellan coaching receiver but good
practical but cut off key committee that
says this you know those can be a
demotion twins but they're also very
popular area for not the Tigers our
nation which didn't really to submit now
cut WIC to chisel a bit it's a boy your
best driving your practice if we create
just about addresses people that's
number two this is this goes with
meditation
this is like visit a set of a suspect
at said how do you serve what Cox
knows it's can I see mr. janely
Mediterraneans
Diamond Mountain at least I always yes
like that no more kind of me just use my
daughter Stein United snap it and I
don't you my early days I used to do I'm
sure yes my company got behind an
organization that goes to shut-ins or
lonely people who can't cook for
themselves
my companion
- the standard sewing them my husband is
a stable reading himself but that it's a
hadith move them off because total
religion team of social with sebum
control of its him but I take Dhamma it
was really beautiful poetry crassness
sadness to grow oysters not your today
why thank you
literally first of Avani our kid family
touch their nose the pleasure it's very
same again I just was it's a CBI but
understand that was always a beautiful
thing the Bolshevik regime I wish I
didn't have a bowl of pasta yeah no Mia
Bullough
dreamy damage but the bush they are the
most turtle machine it opens you bow and
applause Thomas cravat wash yourself say
when you Manya
but further than you know get this verse
a yes Chet it's illusion you can teach
service we wash it up with Chad because
you're going to put on wash this don't
owe me your process you know you need to
some terms know my system those are the
stories filtrate that bring you might
know that you know it's it's just
beautiful see but chef in the flesh
really the most efficient reads
know how you're building seeds for
health extensive attachments there
dissimilar metal yeah went I love my
physics was serving his most Lorena and
last 'no Geshe Michael chinchilla but
you know I was a guy living in New York
yeah both should I become coasters of
New York
I know many my own I mean I was busy
looking for you
teaching abilities I got mighty ago
buddy Lester Patel rubbish at sea level
Minneapolis you question is yeah number
of surgeries interested okay house at
the house great which I don't shut up
what get it off of SEMA middle or a
really cool partner both your know what
kind of seductive things
thank you it's no I never had to take
the subway I just take taxis and you
cook ten years on the magrav sick taxi
okay fifteen please okay anyway long
story short
Daniel Joseph when I bumped into give
you my best guess my club uncut was now
it I knew it I didn't wanna years not
knowing dodgy he did basically reflect
that no interest that resilient of my
upset the bullish touch token my arm is
reason in my mr. Danny a game of
yourself ready justify my job and took
over all day yeah well your sister
aboard a stellar about it they say be
but the samurais never yes I said with
major isn't it
each I wish my god - yeah super this law
right a miss that ball car whenever she
really civility monster typically is
mania my gosh reason s my life change
yeah parody Gomez reason is menu ASEAN
economies material Nezhat in a glad I
was able Sheffield and Ida you were
plugging in like that a project sick as
this vast damage them it might open
their personality specialist right yeah
but it changes this man trader gets an
estate at the track this man attended
should give up are basically made this
regionals in New York
Stella one of the page you never got
service
successful dreaming but paying bills
bills at noise samwich centimeter tactic
of the ocean populated in this magical
anyplace it's functioning do it my god
which it to me did that say CI yogi
Steven God thank you spasiba so maybe in
three years you can imagine chance three
it goes up with exam I purchase top
probably do a get the three jewels II
must polish a seam and then download
Burchett brothers ship study study study
it's a transistor transistor chaser you
gotta keep studying I'm not a writer
perchance it the number two should date
him let's do the two husbands tight
cetera so we're gonna teach you two
husbands to talk about dependent
origination the topic ID model from
Oceanus crostini car banjos new exam
Estevez Mazama to show mr. Peter
P a ravine I say Jay JJ hmm yeah Maria
so Jenny's my kid Jania - like you know
karate bunker
okay we set it up this way I'm a working
mom yeah I'm a new woman up what made
for centuries yeah that's better
you know birth control didn't work for
me what the lair shed in any event you
know being liberated woman means pretty
much basically my husband is written as
my church doors little buddy but I
bought it yeah as opposed to it
yeah sure damn said about the
pudding I cook yeah I just got told to
Tony Howard a surgeon so that's my life
the is just about exhausted yet doctor
she found the setup today is that my
boss called me and my boss said what the
person to reconcile ourselves to the
company the office you better not be
late yeah faster because we have an
important that much done let's assume I
don't have state just normally Anthony
Los Angeles thought of essentially say
yes my job I say okay I'll be there
after tomorrow at this Minnie's
so what do i do well first I gotta get
to yeah I also got some of it is good
how is gonna shock your grades today
God's answers in the chest
okay listen mommy's gonna sit meeting
tomorrow
mom what's inside what time is it
everything away take that Abby said the
vignette
stretcher solution set is got emotional
place they usually say to be dressed for
school by 6's chest trauma but it's got
no your score identify mr. Torres so
rocky Aramis might be shades and Robert
is gonna be done at a much narrower
mother with Gerald
how to shop alright okay so you know I
make husband you know I make the husband
happy that yeah
del we'll just be honest I'm not even I
made him dinner so I don't thirsty up to
get W motion everything's cool that's
selfish aw I wake up at 6:00
yeah breast knows my taste that's this
and I go into the case rooms I'm ready
go ahead over that thought or having a
pillow fight and you did the
stone jelly what are you doing
I told you yesterday what are they
stomach says al-gaddafi stamina manage
asterisk you are the two ladies
family-orientated oh my god get to work
yeah profession that I bought dope
circularize know the presentation me
goodbye it really nothing about say
about that I'm exhausted I understand
yeah make some nice dinner for us go to
this store I'm gonna make some sushi
from scratch
yes sociological Laird establish a
roster 3mph job being and I drag my
stuff yeah look at the imagery so that
dr. Pratt just yet very common clean
Roger Roger is it's more action now and
I just want to press the actual galaxy
Homer prevent revoke our Zilla what
you take a little fresh stuff what did
you say
stutters Casella I'm stupid
I didn't do anything stupid I just went
shopping to buy this whole beautiful
dinner I love them in if I tell Papa yet
I have yet sit it's not my fault but
then you forget each other oh yeah bro
stuck with my husband I think I tell our
audience dismissal but you want the
point they came out of nowhere
he came on on Rustin yet older why what
do you why would you do that to me honey
stop so I jumped at the Jewish fault
didn't you my you have it now so what
just happened so that was the place I
saw three main things happened that he
but you're my sister how much Nicole
here which husband got quite remind
she's but I suppose this makes a mess
but Ella delivered at it yeah
Maria okay well she's my money and
Wednesday s you must are still not sure
but that my husband is this status on
much it's not my fault house but look at
the rhenium is my fault
Daniel I have enough oh my god husband
number two not my father but cut the
flesh Lord tak mush Nehemiah mean as a
shawl knock off now
well no that's how my real husband got
into
off - there she goes - ah oh yeah
look at a chalice and brush through New
Zealand i DT but I'm talking about
lenient at all and as a way I could give
me but he meant that way yeah sitting
idly watching the MIT ID in blandina to
actually you know what resulting
profession Aeneas the Bunsen even also
there's still a dead phone Mosier
number two husband love them but it did
I see what
yeah this has been coming this way
there's much a bracelet that came up on
my so what is it called crocodile is a
by itself well there's a word called the
gunshot Daksha think I'm sure it's one
of your 21 words
yeah I mean mr. tides in this to the
question who's understand them Islamic
access the slower at the torch opposite
opposite opposite opposite I'd of
current motion tyrannical dynamo just a
vatsnik a dinosaur just about anything
that you booted so she saw us but we
work better host know my Sarge I am a
drama stoppage EMU that a Muslim because
were hardwired were born as gives you
Michael said today the most American me
sir shames Tamir brisket Nana's from
found
indigent go back one and that happens to
at the present tomorrow replace a
supernatural mr. Krasner precise
becoming of is imperceptible Amara
Shizuka I see no Maria specificity
okay out of five minutes when your pets
minute so to wrap it up that's dependent
origination
that's it is a resource garcinia the
pasta Tom and the dark see it's a
question in my and the most earnest I
didn't have time question but I said
yes
I really like how during the lecture you
said the pinellas collective reality of
college that is my specialty and really
kind of struck me and now miniature
Penelope this eternal war are totally
monogamous there are things that we do
at much of a corrosive Asian actor
magellan compare a mr. black investor I
steal or pervasive ignorance beginning
is five times this condition ecologist
will nip any money and business the
Christopher J is near sick dance record
over Teresa my name is process recently
destination ecologist Simon any
productive adverse decisions circle my
bottom simply born but that matters to
me estimate Hakeem Olajuwon cycling
vodka but can you sleep extraordinary of
us near balad Hatem rebirth by your
decision you know among little bit
finish then Peters in the worst Obama
which gives to just world
- establishes that a seminary through
the chemo presence the current cabinet
but you're hearing now is this by doing
some serious work city was not about the
fragility of gosh
[Music]
but his seminars and about the best
solutions ethical work is a right the
more the better etc also is trying to
understand the
when you might absolutely Rado selfish a
the first time nurse does not
necessarily
[Music]
to partial
yes
[Music]
superboy sure